<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Brainiac]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Brainiac</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:23:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:23:11 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[Rijul Kumar]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>Rijul Kumar</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[PRODUCTS]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Multi column
Blank container
Monday, November 18, 2024, 1:17:31 PM
— Last Modified Time


Blank container
<img alt="Templates/Business Templates/QR Code.jpg" height="100" src="\lib\media\qr-code.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer" style="width: 100px; max-width: 100%;">

<br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>BWW2806
Title: Programming Your Mind for Success
Speakers: Sugeet &amp; Kaajal Ajmani

Categories: Teaching; New Releases
<br><br><br><br><br>Multi column
Blank container
Overcome Even the Greatest Challenges with Courage and Confidence
by John C. Maxwell


Blank container
<img src="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=k6gHEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">


<br><br>
<br>Embracing hardship as a test of character and use them as rising to the occasion.
<br>Leaders are keepers and communicators of the vision. Bear the responsibility for always seeing the big picture and helping their people to see it.
<br>Values are the heart of your character and your leadership.
<br>Leaders role is not to control people or stay on top of things, but rather guide, energize and excite.
<br>Good leaders deal successfully with the diversity and differences of their team and leverage the for the benefit of the team and organization.
<br><br><br>
<br>
<br><br><br>So true right so true and and what happens is that and people wonder how come I run into these problems all the time have you seen some some people are like they have problems all the time can we shut this off yeah they have problems all the time right and this is what happens it's like it starts building up because you you keep verbalizing the same things over and over again and guess what happens the energy stays with you but in contrast if you start you know people say I'm not motivated to do the work have you have you heard that right now people think that motivation creates momentum but might be true but can momentum create motivation right like I'll give you an example somebody's in very high momentum okay so so Nisha have there been days that you got up in the morning and you didn't want to go into work yeah did you still go in yeah have you tried calling up your boss and saying can you motivate me because I don't feel motivated enough to come in can you try that on Monday yeah you will yeah your boss will be okay with that no he might be mad okay don't try it then yeah she's still willing to try no don't try it don't try it you know naturally we know that now what happens to a lot of people see that's why I played that what happens to a lot of people is that something goes wrong in their business something goes against their expectation and suddenly they feel low and they carry this low energy around and guess what happens they attract more of the same frequency right and they start thinking negative and suddenly they all they have so if you had three people in your team and one person quit or stop showing up suddenly you're some younger people in your team-looking lean. OH 111 biologyaci 05455 healthcare HA isn't the chance tobok you but you but you
 starting to think negative, right? And you start attracting negative energy and before you know it, the two people who were there, they don't, they don't feel good being around you. So always, you know, before you say something or before you think something or when you are thinking something, here's what you have to think also is that where am I going with this? Am I headed in the positive direction or am I headed in the negative direction? Because remember one thing, now you might think, oh, that's not, it's all stupidity, but what if it was true? Right? Now there is a boxing match happening tonight. Right? Mike Tyson is boxing who? Jake Paul. Jake Paul. Jake Paul. Who is he? Who's Jake Paul? A YouTuber. Okay. Yeah. YouTuber who's working on. Now, I watched an interview. The lady is asking, so this guy who posted this also posted the other, other video and he says, it talks about manifestation and how old is Mike Tyson? 58 years old. And how old is that Jake? 27, 28 years old. Okay. So this lady, right? Press reporter. She's asking Mike Tyson, sir, what if you lose? He looks at her, says, I'm going to win. Yes, yes, sir. But what if you lose? Lady, you didn't hear me. I'm going to win. Yes, sir. I understand. But I am going to win. So a lady behind that reporter touched her and said, okay, stop it.
 Because he was getting upset. He was getting upset. And then there's a comment below. This is how he has been from day one. From day one. Now I don't know what the results are going to be. I don't care. But what I'm saying is that that's how you think. That's how you think. And you know what? When is it difficult? When things are going great? It's easy. When things are going in the other direction. That's when it decides. That's when your character shows up. That's when your character shows up. Right? And when you start focusing on little things. Sometimes people start. You know when there are things not going right for them. They start focusing on other people's business. What's the statement that we make about other people's business? What is not your business is none of your business. Now let me tell you. The logic behind that. Because I never like to say something to people and not explain why we say that. Because the thing is we don't know what somebody is going through. We don't know why their business looks the way it looks. Right? And it does not benefit us. Because it will make us think. Negative. Or not so positive. Do we want that? No. No. And how does it matter? How would you like it if you walk into somebody's house and the first question they ask is, so how much do you make? Do we seh all know that that's offensive platform turns out? It's the same thing here. So when you walk into a meeting here, you cannot ask anybody. So how many people do you have in your group? Because it's not going to help you anyway. Because if they were thriving and growing, we would all be talking about it. You don't have to ask. The fact that you are asking tells me that you got doubt. And you're looking to stabilize or strengthen.
 Lengthen that doubt. You're looking for facts. Yes, I'm right. Yeah, it does not work. See, because why do you need to look into somebody else's business? Because it's not going to help you anyway. So why ask that question in the first place? So, you know, I come to know somebody's energy. As soon as I'm with somebody and they start asking me about somebody else's business or talking about somebody else's business, I know this person is not going anywhere. Not going anywhere. Not because they are not good people, but the way they're thinking is wrong. The way they're thinking is wrong because they are interested in somebody else's business. Marcel, you bumped into somebody, right? For contacting, right? He was from some other team that left BWW. And what did you ask me? Why did they leave? And what did I say, Marcel? Same thing. Same thing. I said, don't worry about it. None of my business. I don't know what transpired there, but I don't care. My plan is still here. That's all I care. Because last time Papalado came and did a plan for me, was never. You get what I'm saying. So how does it matter to me who comes, who goes, who stays, who grows? Growing? Yeah, it helps. But growing, I already come to know. Right? When they got up, who was that? Jitu and Neelam. And said, you got 11 legs. Right? That you come to know. Because that is showcased. Nobody is showcasing people. Look at this guy. Nobody. He has nobody on his team. Right? Nobody is talking about that. Because you know what? Nobody wants to know. And you should not want to know also. Right? So don't worry about it. Don't probe. I never asked Sugit. So what happened to that other leg of yours? He's not coming around. First of all, it is embarrassing to Sugit. I don't know.
 Secondly, is it going to help me? Then how does it? It's going to probably hurt you. If at all anything, it's going to hurt me because I'm going to start thinking negatively. And like he said, I'm going to start attracting negative. Right? So why worry about it? And the other thing is, when he talks about positive, you have to seem positive also. Right? You have to seem happy. If you got this constipated look like you really want to rush to the bathroom, nobody wants to be around you. You might be serious about the business. Have you seen some people are very serious about the business? But you see the seriousness on their face also. Right? I don't want to be around them. Right? You want to have fun. You want to have some great jokes. Yeah. I mean. Happy Thanksgiving. Right? Right? Have fun. Enjoy. This should seem like you are enjoying the process of building the business because the business will grow if you are having fun with it. But have fun while working the business also. There is work involved. Right? There is work involved. And don't worry about what other people are saying. Do you know what echo chamber is? Okay. It's an analogy they use for dogs. So dogs, some dogs cannot realize their own echoes. So they might sit there, lazing around and they bark. Just generally. Oh! Right? They hear their bark coming back. They say, oh, there is seriously something wrong. Oh! Oh! Oh! You also think there is something wrong? Oh! Oh! Oh! And now the whole neighborhood dogs are barking. The one who started it does not even know why he started it. Right? That's called echo chamber. So a lot of people are living in this echo chamber of negativity. Right? They are looking for things. Is somebody barking? Then I want to bark also. Right? The first person who started the bark does not even know why he started. Right? The first person who started the bark does not even know why he started.
 And that's the story. So don't worry about that. Focus on your business work hard. We are Sushma and I are headed tomorrow 8 AM in the morning. I don't know whether Mohit and Koki are you on, please make sure they don't forget. Otherwise we'll be stranded here. Our plane will take off with all the bags. Okay. They are supposed to come pick us up at 8 AM in the morning. If he doesn't show up, I will show up. I know, but. Because I'm up at 4 AM. You are always up at. Now he can work out with our bags. Right? Oh yeah, he has a 5.30 AM plan. Happily the man's been contacting everywhere and he suddenly says, Saji, so when it is 2 PM, 2 PM in India, that's a good time for us to show the plan. I said only if you're not sleeping because it's 3.30 in the morning here. 3.30 in the morning. Why is it? No, Saji, it's not 3.30 in the morning. I said, it is 3.30 in the morning. Oh, I thought it would be 6 AM. No, he thought it was 12.30 AM. Yeah, he thought it was 12.30. Right after pace. Other way. It's a right after pace. I'll show the plan. But then he set it up for 5.30 AM. 5.30 AM. Wow. Wow. Right? So it's how you look at things. Everything is about how you look at things. Everything. It doesn't matter whether your business is going forward, whether it's life, unless you have a life threatening, something happening. Right? Let's find the good in everything that's going on in our life. Everything. Because there is some good. Right? You might have to look hard sometimes. Right? But there is something good all the time. And that's how you become the person that attracts everyone. Since you started off on this, I want to cover another cardinal rule. So we have, we are in a people business and we want to make sure everybody is comfortable with the vibe we have here. Right? So there are some cardinal rules that have been put into place mainly to protect ourselves.
 and protect others who are becoming part of our team. So this, what Saji just mentioned is a cardinal rule which is don't embarrass anyone. This is an embarrassing question, so don't embarrass anyone. Now another cardinal rule is about being alone with a person of the opposite gender. And I'll tell you why that is in place. To be honest, when I heard it first, I thought how archaic is that cardinal rule? How archaic is that? We're in such modern ages and how can you place such a cardinal rule and explain why? And off once in a while is not such an issue. But if week after week, if I was going to travel to the APA hotel with Ashwin, first he'll eat all my food. But besides that problem, here's what happens. Two individuals traveling, just the two of them, right? Traveling together. Before you know it, you are talking about yourself and opening up to that other person. And you know, who knows? Who knows what kind of feelings are going to develop? Maybe in just one person. And then that's going to make the other person uncomfortable. Right? Or let's say you are like SK is here and Mrs. Santosh is not here. And if she or Marcel's example, right? Alicia cannot come to PACE on Fridays because she works in a beauty salon and one of their busiest days is Fridays. How secure would she feel if every week Marcel was driving to the meeting for an hour and a half each way with another woman?
 Right? So those are things that are thought of and that is why these cardinal rules are in place. So if I had to give a right to Ashwin, bad example here because we adhere to the cardinal rules but if I had to give a right to Ashwin I would make sure either another male or another female was in the car. So there's three people in the car and… Chiara. A female. No, definitely not Ayaan because he and Ashwin will eat my food. But do you see the point here? Right? Now if what I said here does not make sense to you, please have a discussion with one of us about the importance of sticking to the cardinal rules because there is value, there is a lot of value in that. Yes, it's so much easier to not take this into account and whenever you want hop into someone's car. An off situation here and there is not the problem. It's a problem when you… And that's why… When Brittany needs a right, what we try to do is we keep moving her around like a football team to other people's car. Right? I mean… Yeah, I mean the thing is that she wants to come to the meeting. She lives quite far from here but she wants to show up. That is amazing. That is phenomenal. A lot of people will make an excuse and say I log in online, you know, but she wants to come. So we make sure that she gets a ride and we try to make sure that she's not going with the same person for a long time. Because you know, we want to make sure that we are teaching the right things. That's… Okay? We are taking out for Brittany when we do that. Yeah. And I'll explain why. Let's say it was someone like Jackie. I'm saying the jokes, right? Sometimes people make jokes that are not appropriate. That might just be them. What… … … … … … … … … …
 What if it was making Britney uncomfortable? Right? You don't know. You don't know. There are certain jokes that a person of another gender might make or just another whatever origin might make. But having a third person in there hopefully diffuses the situation so it's not just the two of you arguing about politics or something totally unrelated to this business. And that is why we say this about two people who might not be platinums, who might not have the maturity of having led a team travelling together. So can we make an effort to understand this and even if you don't understand it just say okay I'm just going to do it because even though it does not make sense I'll just do it. That's what we did in the beginning. It made no sense. We said you know what? A lot of things they talked about as far as the rules were concerned did not make sense to us. But we said you know what? I want a business. We want a business. We want a growing team. The last thing we want is to create confusion. I didn't want to be a rebel and fail in the business. You know? What am I going to prove? Yeah. Right? There was no cause that I was fighting for. I was not Martin Luther King. Right? So. We knew for a fact that abiding by the cardinal rules was not going to stop us from building a large team. So why not do it? Right. So while we are on that topic, let me also tell you. So let's say Alex, you are at the function and let's say somebody from Tanmay and Rashmi's team know that you live in Jersey City and they come up to you and ask you for a ride. First thing you have to do is say, I am going in that direction, but let me check with my upline. Now he, so does that mean Saket can tell you that? Okay. Yeah. It's okay for you to take that person. No. You know why? Tell me why.
 Alex. Yeah. It's they say you have to be able to get the common upline involved. What does the common upline mean? That means Sushma is one leg. I am one leg and the common upline. So who's the common upline between Tanmay Rashmi and Saket? Till Sugit is aware and gives the green signal. You cannot take that. Why? Tell me why. Hold on, Sushma. This is the people who... You got your chance. You had the mic. Did you hear me jumping in? Did you hear me jumping in? Okay, that's good. Okay, yeah. No, I'm guessing he would know whatever stuff is going on. Yeah. No, but Sushma is right. What if that guy is a serial killer? Or what if that guy is like, you know, he carries... No. Like small packets with him all the time. Or has a warrant on his name. Or a warrant on his name. Who knows? You don't know. But I know every person in this room. Every person. And I also know what's going on in their life. For the most part. For the most part. For the people who talk to me. Right? Now, because you might crack a joke about... Oh, this husband and wife. They are fighting, man. And this guy's five and him might be fighting. Yeah. Right? So I just told the India team this morning. I said, unless you are a platinum. Don't give advice on house buying. Marriages. Or anything. Don't go and tell somebody that... I think you should change your wife. Right? Because... Now, you are laughing at all this. But let me tell you. We had a situation. Not changing wife. But somebody... Some guy was not coming to the meeting on time. Right? He was always late.
 core guy big pin this other big pin asked him so no no no just ask just asked him hey how come you don't come on time he said oh because i have this job situation and this guy is like pretty high level okay his job is like he's like a senior vp or something like some like sakit so he said my job you know nowadays we have a situation because of which i am running a little late so he said you should change your job forget his own downline he's telling cross lane also so just be careful right just be careful and the other the thing is we don't market anything within our team and if i come to know that you know sriman bought something at a huge discount that and i'm also looking for it and if i asked sriman then that's fine but sriman cannot just because he got a discount go ahead and tell everybody i got a discount or i got a discount do you want a discount do you want a discount and build a connection with that guy saying okay you give them 20 give me 10 out of that right this is no no other deals should happen here okay we should remember all that and why do we do the meetings tell me to grow our business how do we grow our business new people new people let's all work on making sure this team grows to a our goal was 100 people right 100 people this year we still got time we can do it i mean i know a lot of people couldn't come today i know ritual is still on the screen he's getting better did you learn any are you sitting on the floor or something look she's pretty low right i guess she's behind that's why now she's yeah see no no so a ritual must be sitting on a ladder or something okay so still still still still still
 Okay. You know, I see a lot of people. Now here's another thing. We are one team. Our message is grow. Let's all grow. This time Sushma and I are going on Achievers. Let me tell you. Yesterday, Sushma was asking me, talking to somebody about doing a meeting. And I said, let's do it this Saturday. Sushma said, but this Saturday, we are not here. This is yesterday. And I'm thinking, where are we going this Saturday? Yeah. So he looks at his calendar. Every time he's talking to someone, he's going through his calendar. He says, Saturday is open. Let's do it. He promised like 10 people meetings on Saturday and Sunday. You know why? If you guys all were going with me or a lot of you were going with me, I would not forget. I would not forget. Can you promise to join with us? Yes. Okay. Pick a year guys. Pick 25, pick 26, pick 27. But we want you with us. Because this one, we didn't go to the last one. Right? We didn't want to go. This one, we didn't want to go also. I had a big long conversation with Sugit. Saying, I'm not coming. He said, no, you have to come. You have to build dreams for your team. But we need you with us. I know next year, we got PK and Sonia going with us. We know, Michelle going with us. Right? Michelle and Robin coming with us. To San Diego. And we know that next, the year after that, a whole bunch more of you will come. Right? We want you with us. Okay? Because there's no, it's no fun. I mean, rides and all. I don't do rides and all. If you guys come, then I'll go. Even if I'm scared, I'll go on the rides. Just to see how scared you are. Okay? So with that, we are done. Here's back to our amazing host, Jackie! 
<br><br><br>Here is the summary that I have written
```
{Summary section}
```
#Business
#Meeting-Notes]]></description><link>business\meeting-notes\pase\2024-11-15-kumar-team-pase-meeting.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Business/Meeting Notes/PASE/2024-11-15 - Kumar Team PASE Meeting.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Rijul Kumar]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:17:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\qr-code.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;lib\media\qr-code.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>